## Sabastian Storm White Belser, MBA

sswbelser.com sswbelser@gmail.com (510) 847-6982 linkedin.com/in/sswbelser github.com/sswbelser @sswbelser

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I worked several years in human resources and operations management, before pursuing my passion of web development. I taught myself for several months and joined a bootcamp, through which I have been building several full stack web apps. I am a quick learner, I have worked in very diverse environments, and I am excited to bring my unique perspective to your company.

#### **EDUCATION**

2015

General Assembly, San Francisco
Web Development Immersive

2014

Golden Gate University, San Francisco
MBA - Management

2012

University of California, Davis BA - Sociology: Organizational Studies

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScript/jQuery Bcrypt Node.js/Express Unity/Quintus/Phasor Ruby on Rails Mocha HTML5/CSS3 GitHub Bootstrap Heroku Swift HRIS/ATS MongoDB CRM SQL/PostgreSQL **Operations Management** Underscore Recruiting

## WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

## Extraterrestrial Excape | Heroku | GitHub

- I built a basic Quintus-powered platformer game in four days to explore level design and backend functionalities of a web app
- Technologies used: JavaScript, Quintus, jQuery, jQuery Validation, Underscore, Node.js/Express, Bootstrap, AJAX, Bcrypt, MongoDB, Mongoose, Mocha, GitHub, and Heroku

## atCon | Heroku | GitHub

- I was the lead dev for a group of four, and in four days we built a social network web app for conferences
- Technologies used: Ruby on Rails, Bootstrap, jQuery, jQuery Validation, AJAX, Paperclip, AWS SDK, RSpec, LinkedIn API, Bcrypt, PostgreSQL, GitHub, and Heroku

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **General Assembly**

Web Development Immersive Student | 2015-2015

- Creating multiple full stack MEAN and Ruby on Rails web apps per week
- Pair programming, working with teams through project weeks, and GitHub workflow
- Applying new languages, frameworks, and libraries to assignments throughout the week, and for pet projects

## Conestoga-Rovers & Associates / GHD Inc.

Human Resources Generalist | 2014-2015

- HRIS and ATS administration: PeopleSoft, ADP, Taleo, elearning software, and legacy systems
- Process analyses and consolidation for company merger

## **Bauer's Intelligent Transportation**

Account Manager | 2013-2014

- Managed operations of the University of California bus system
- Project management to increase operational efficiency

# **Berkshire Hathaway Homestate Companies**

Human Resources Assistant | 2012-2013

- HRIS and ATS administration: ADP, SharedHR, Workday, and legacy systems
- Benefits and recruiting administration

# **Specialized Transportation Services/Tipsy Taxi**

Director | 2009-2012

- Responsible for total functionality of STS/TT; both operations and finances
- Hired, trained, and mentored 30+ direct reports